datingadvicesecrets.com 2013-04-02

# Site Info

ABOUT US

DatingAdviceSecrets.com is a website I started because I wanted to be a positive force in helping single men out there who are having trouble meeting women, point them in the right direction, learn to become men who can naturally attract women and live more happy and fulfilling lives.  
a  
My vision for this website is to bring together all the leading experts in dating advice, and bring them here to share for free and the benefit of single men from around the world.

I started this website as a hobby in 2008. The website has grown beyond my expectations, and I have big plans for it in the near future!

Please visit us again soon, I am constantly changing things around here.

-Josh

TERMS & CONDITIONS

DatingAdviceSecrets.com(TM) and it’s affiliate sites is made available for entertainment purposes only.

While DatingAdviceSecrets.com and it’s affiliates uses reasonable efforts to make sure all content on this site is current and accurate, using the advice on this site is at your own risk.

I am not a doctor, lawyer or therapist, and you should consult with a professional if you need help.

You agree also not to use any of this content available here for you in anyway that would infringe on copyright.

You should assume everything on this website is copyrighted, and should not use any of the content without giving it proper credit (along with a link back to the source).

Many people have worked hard to produce this content and make it free for you, please respect this.

PRIVACY POLICY

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

datingadvicesecrets.com  
297 Desmarteau  
Montreal, Quebec H7N5P7  
Canada  
josh@datingadvicesecrets.com  
1450696108

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support [help desk software](http://www.rhinosupport.com/).

DATING COLUMNISTS/WRITERS:

Hi, my name is Rhen and I help run this site, and take care of the content side of things around here.

If you have expertise in dating and would like to write for us, we pay $20 per 750 word+ blog post/article. And this goes up based on performance metrics, such as # of comments, replying to comments, etc. Could go up to $50 per blog post if services are retained for more than 6 months.

We’re looking for original, useful content (1x or 2x/week) to the male singles demographic aged 20 to 40.

Topics could range from today’s single scene, your adventures in your single life, sex, and anything that could appeal to the single male demographic. (age 20-45)

Expertise in this field is a plus. You are not required to blog exclusively here. But will be required to contribute on a regular basis depending on quality of writing.

Please submit some writing samples to and I’ll get back in touch within a couple days time if there is a fit: [rhen@datingadvicesecrets.com](mailto:rhen@datingadvicesecrets.com)  

DATING COMPANIES/EXPERTS/PARTNERS:

If you are a dating expert and want to get your name/company out to a very targeted demographic, you’re at the right place. With over 150,000 unique singles that visit this site every month you will be talking to the right people, 100% of the time. You will get an nice author bio mentioned at the bottom of each post, that links back to your website, for increased traffic and business (for free).

I can help syndicate your content to a mass audience here. Please submit inquiries to:[rhen@datingadvicesecrets.com](mailto:rhen@datingadvicesecrets.com)

FOR ANYTHING ELSE:

Suggestions, comments, etc. To contact me, simply use the contact form below.

I’m also reachable by phone at 1-514-667-5568 from 10am – 6pm (Eastern Time)

And via snail mail (not recommended:)):

RKM  
+1.5146675568  
Fax: +1.5146675568  
276 Desmarteau  
Laval, H7N5P7  
CA
